[
{"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Which artist has the highest streamed song on spotify", "answer":"Ed Sheeran"},
{"category":"MUSIC", "question":"What card game appeared in a #1 Lady Gaga song", "answer":"Poker"},
{"category":"MUSIC", "question":"Which classic composer was deaf", "answer":"Beethoven"},
{"category":"CELEBRITIES", "question":"In 2021 Kanye West legally changed his name to what two letter letter name?", "answer":"Ye"},
{"category":"CELEBRITIES", "question":"Which boxer was known as 'The People's Champion'", "answer":"Muhammad Ali"},
{"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"An involuntary contraction of the diaphragm is also known as a:", "answer":"Hiccup"},
{"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"What is the chemical symbol for Potassium", "answer":"K"},
{"category":"SCIENCE", "question":"What is the chemical formula for water", "answer":"H2O"},
{"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Area 51 is located in which US state", "answer":"Nevada"},
{"category":"GEOGRAPHY", "question":"Which long, thin country spans over half of the South American west coast", "answer":"Chile"},
{"category":"SPORTS", "question":"What is the ball used in badminton", "answer":"Shuttlecock"},
{"category":"SPORTS", "question":"Who won the Euros in 2021", "answer":"Italy"},
{"category":"SPORTS", "question":"How high off the ground is a basketball hoop in feet", "answer":"10"},
{"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"What is the only mammal capable of sustained flight", "answer":"Bat"},
{"category":"ANIMALS", "question":"From which animal do we get venison", "answer":"Deer"},
{"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"How many ships does each player have in Battleship", "answer":"5"},
{"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"Which chess piece cannot move backwards", "answer":"Pawn"},
{"category":"BOARD GAMES", "question":"How many points is the letter J worth in Scrabble", "answer":"8"},
{"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"What does GPU stand for", "answer":"Graphical Processing Unit"},
{"category":"TECHNOLOGY", "question":"In what year was the first iPhone released", "answer":"2007"},
{"category":"BUSINESS", "question":"What product did Amazon initially start out selling", "answer":"Books"},
{"category":"LITERACY", "question":"What word shares its name with a rocket and a mythological God", "answer":"Apollo"},
{"category":"LITERACY", "question":"Spell rhythm", "answer":"R-H-Y-T-H-M"},
{"category":"LITERACY", "question":"Other than Germany, whose official language is German", "answer":"Austria"},
{"category":"YOUTUBE", "question":"What is the most disliked video on youtube", "answer":"Youtube Rewind 2016"},
{"category":"YOUTUBE", "question":"What is the most viewed diss track of all time", "answer":"The Fall of Jake Paul"},
{"category":"COMICS", "question":"What superhero sidekick is known as the Boy Wonder", "answer":"Robin"},
{"category":"FILM", "question":"Who directed E.T", "answer":"Steven Spielberg"},
{"category":"FILM", "question":"Name the Dreamworks film starring British rats", "answer":"Flushed Away"},
{"category":"FILM", "question":"Which 4 legged mammal is Shrek's best friend", "answer":"Donkey"},
{"category":"FILM", "question":"What is the highest grossing R rated movie of all time", "answer":"Joker"},
{"category":"ANIME", "question":"What does Naruto want to become", "answer":"Hokage"},
{"category":"ANIME", "question":"How many dragon balls are there", "answer":"7"},
{"category":"CLOTHING", "question":"What Ancient Roman garment is also an anagram of the word goat", "answer":"Ryuk"},
{"category":"CLOTHING", "question":"What shoes named after a basketball player does Miles wear in the movie Spider-Man: ITSV", "answer":"Joran 1 Retro Highs"},
{"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"Who is friends with Jesse Pinkman, Badger and Skinny Pete", "answer":"Combo"},
{"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"In The Boys, what is the name of Homelander's son", "answer":"Ryan"},
{"category":"TELEVISION", "question":"You think this is bad? This? This:", "answer":"Chicanery"},
{"category":"GAMING", "question":"Knuckles from Sonic is what animal?", "answer":"Echidna"},
{"category":"GAMING", "question":"Who is the main character from the Zelda series?", "answer":"Link"},
{"category":"GAMING", "question":"Who came first, Mario or Sonic?", "answer":"Mario"},
{"category":"GAMING", "question":"The character of Mario first appeared in which other Nintendo character's game", "answer":"Donkey Kong"},
{"category":"MATHS", "question":"What is the cube root of 1000", "answer":"10"},
{"category":"MATHS", "question":"On what number is the decimal system based", "answer":"10"},
{"category":"MATHS", "question":"What is 10 x 10 - 10", "answer":"90"},
{"category":"HISTORY", "question":"In which decade did Neil Armstrong land on the moon", "answer":"60s"},
{"category":"HISTORY", "question":"What title was given to Ancient Egyptian rulers", "answer":"Pharaoh"},
{"category":"HISTORY", "question":"How many US Presidents have been assassinated", "answer":"4"},
{"category":"FOOD", "question":"What type of food is pitta", "answer":"Bread"},
{"category":"FOOD", "question":"Is wholemeal bread brown or white", "answer":"Brown"},
{"category":"DRINKS", "question":"How is a drink served when it is described as frappe", "answer":"With crushed ice"},
{"category":"DRINKS", "question":"Name the oldest fizzy soft drink, which shares its name with a type of fruit", "answer":"Dr Pepper"},
{"category":"FANDOME", "question":"In which month and year did TMU fall", "answer":"March 2021"},
{"category":"FANDOME", "question":"Noah Roach belongs to what ancient clan", "answer":"Shinklebottom"}
]